<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>UKS Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:12:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to stream Global Citizen&#8217;s Power Our Planet: Live in Paris concert Thursday</title>
		<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/how-to-stream-global-citizens-power-our-planet-live-in-paris-concert-thursday/</link>
					<comments>https://uks.online.mills.edu/how-to-stream-global-citizens-power-our-planet-live-in-paris-concert-thursday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://uks.online.mills.edu/?p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Music superstars Lenny Kravitz, Billie Eilish and H.E.R. will team with advocacy nonprofit Global Citizen for a free concert in front of the Eiffel Tower designed to convince world leaders to take further action against climate change. Global Citizen CEO Hugh Evans says the summit is an opportunity for governments and global banks to collaborate...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/how-to-stream-global-citizens-power-our-planet-live-in-paris-concert-thursday/">How to stream Global Citizen&#8217;s Power Our Planet: Live in Paris concert Thursday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Music superstars Lenny Kravitz, Billie Eilish and H.E.R. will team with advocacy nonprofit Global Citizen for a free concert in front of the Eiffel Tower designed to convince world leaders to take further action against climate change.</p>



<p>Global Citizen CEO Hugh Evans says the summit is an opportunity for governments and global banks to collaborate to jump start climate projects stalled by the COVID-19 pandemic. He hopes &#8220;Power Our Planet&#8221; will encourage leaders to take advantage of that opportunity and provide the $16.7 billion in outstanding climate financing promised in 2009 to lower-income countries. He is also seeking to advance reforms at the World Bank to make up to $1 trillion in additional financing available.</p>



<p>The Eiffel Tower event is part of the Global Citizen initiative, announced last month at the Global Citizen NOW conference in New York, supporting Barbados Prime Minister Mia Mottley&#8217;s call to rewrite the rules of global development banks and relieve the debts of lower-income countries to increase funding for climate adaptation projects.</p>



<p>Global Citizen has shown for years, especially with its A-list concerts in New York&#8217;s Central Park, that it can generate action by having cultural leaders mobilize their supporters. And artists like Kravitz plan to motivate fans to &#8220;act today to save tomorrow.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/how-to-stream-global-citizens-power-our-planet-live-in-paris-concert-thursday/">How to stream Global Citizen&#8217;s Power Our Planet: Live in Paris concert Thursday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://uks.online.mills.edu/how-to-stream-global-citizens-power-our-planet-live-in-paris-concert-thursday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MLB to play 2024 regular season game at Birmingham&#8217;s historic Rickwood Field</title>
		<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/mlb-to-play-2024-regular-season-game-at-birminghams-historic-rickwood-field/</link>
					<comments>https://uks.online.mills.edu/mlb-to-play-2024-regular-season-game-at-birminghams-historic-rickwood-field/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://uks.online.mills.edu/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rickwood Field in Birmingham, Alabama, the oldest professional ballpark in the United States and the longtime home of Negro League Baseball games, will host its first Major League Baseball game one year from today when the St. Louis Cardinals play the San Francisco Giants on June 20, 2024. &#8220;I can’t believe it,&#8221; Hall of Famer...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/mlb-to-play-2024-regular-season-game-at-birminghams-historic-rickwood-field/">MLB to play 2024 regular season game at Birmingham&#8217;s historic Rickwood Field</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Rickwood Field in Birmingham, Alabama, the oldest professional ballpark in the United States and the longtime home of Negro League Baseball games, will host its first Major League Baseball game one year from today when the St. Louis Cardinals play the San Francisco Giants on June 20, 2024.</p>



<p>&#8220;I can’t believe it,&#8221; Hall of Famer Willie Mays, 92, who played for the Birmingham Black Barons, said in a statement. &#8220;I never thought I’d see in my lifetime a Major League Baseball game being played on the very field where I played baseball as a teenager. It has been 75 years since I played for the Birmingham Black Barons at Rickwood Field, and to learn that my Giants and the Cardinals will play a game there and honor the legacy of the Negro Leagues and all those who came before them is really emotional for me. We can’t forget what got us here and that was the Negro Leagues for so many of us.&#8221;</p>



<p>Major League Baseball is scheduled to make the official announcement Tuesday morning, with the game played at 7 p.m. ET (Fox) celebrating Juneteenth while also honoring and paying tribute to the Negro Leagues. The teams will be wearing Negro League uniforms celebrating the history of the two cities, with the Cardinals the designated home team.</p>



<p>&#8220;I am so excited that Birmingham will be able to share the magic and legacy of Rickwood Field with Major League Baseball&#8217;s millions of fans,&#8221; Birmingham Mayor Randall L. Woodfin said in a statement. &#8220;America&#8217;s oldest professional ballpark still echoes with the sounds of the legends who graced this field. I want to thank Major League Baseball for sharing this vision to commemorate Juneteenth and celebrate the Negro Leagues in the Magic City.&#8221;</p>



<p>This will be the first MLB game played in a historic Negro Leagues ballpark, and certainly will not be the last. Historic Hinchliffe Stadium in Paterson, New Jersey, which re-opened last month, is likely to host a game in the future. It was the home field of Paterson native Larry Doby, the first Black player to integrate the American League.</p>



<p>&#8220;This opportunity to pay tribute to the Negro Leagues as the Giants and Cardinals play a regular season game at this iconic location is a great honor,&#8221; MLB commissioner Rob Manfred said in a statement. &#8220;The legacy of the Negro Leagues and its greatest living player, Willie Mays, is one of excellence and perseverance. We look forward to sharing the stories of the Negro Leagues throughout this event next year.&#8221;</p>



<p>The Birmingham Black Barons of the Negro Leagues played their home games at Rickwood Field from 1924-1960, with Mays starting his career with the Barons in 1948. Some of the greatest players to grace the sport played games at Rickwood Field, including Hall of Famers Hank Aaron, Jackie Robinson, Doby, Monte Irvin, Ernie Banks, Cool Papa Bell, Satchel Paige, Roy Campanella, Josh Gibson, Oscar Charleston, Buck Leonard, Rube Foster, Roberto Clemente, Babe Ruth, Reggie Jackson, Frank Robinson, Joe DiMaggio, Stan Musial, Yogi Berra, Mickey Mantle, Duke Snider and&nbsp; Honus Wagner.</p>



<p>Rickwood Field, listed on the National Register of Historic Places, was also the site of the last Negro League World Series game in October 1948.</p>



<p>&#8220;To connect our past with the present is so important to our organization and going to such a historic and iconic place as Rickwood Field will allow us to do just that,&#8221; Giants president Larry Baer said in a statement, &#8220;while also connecting with fans and communities outside of our regular Major League cities.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/mlb-to-play-2024-regular-season-game-at-birminghams-historic-rickwood-field/">MLB to play 2024 regular season game at Birmingham&#8217;s historic Rickwood Field</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://uks.online.mills.edu/mlb-to-play-2024-regular-season-game-at-birminghams-historic-rickwood-field/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Igor Stimac on getting red card for interrupting Pakistan player: ‘I will do it again when needed to protect our boys’</title>
		<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/igor-stimac-on-getting-red-card-for-interrupting-pakistan-player-i-will-do-it-again-when-needed-to-protect-our-boys/</link>
					<comments>https://uks.online.mills.edu/igor-stimac-on-getting-red-card-for-interrupting-pakistan-player-i-will-do-it-again-when-needed-to-protect-our-boys/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://uks.online.mills.edu/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>India coach Igor Stimac interrupts Pakistan&#8217;s Abdullah Iqbal from taking a throw in (LEFT). The incident led to a showdown between both sets of players. Igor Stimac on getting red card for interrupting Pakistan player: ‘I will do it again when needed to protect our boys’ Bengaluru:&#160;India head coach Igor Stimac on Thursday defended his...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/igor-stimac-on-getting-red-card-for-interrupting-pakistan-player-i-will-do-it-again-when-needed-to-protect-our-boys/">Igor Stimac on getting red card for interrupting Pakistan player: ‘I will do it again when needed to protect our boys’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>India coach Igor Stimac interrupts Pakistan&#8217;s Abdullah Iqbal from taking a throw in (LEFT). The incident led to a showdown between both sets of players.</p>



<p>Igor Stimac on getting red card for interrupting Pakistan player: ‘I will do it again when needed to protect our boys’</p>



<p><strong>Bengaluru:</strong>&nbsp;India head coach Igor Stimac on Thursday defended his actions during the team’s 4-0 win over Pakistan in its SAFF Championship opener here, saying he “will do it again” to protect his players against “unjustified decisions”.</p>



<p>Stimac was shown a red card for interrupting the actions of an opposition player deliberately at the Sree Kanteerava Stadium on Wednesday.</p>



<p>“Football is all about passion, especially when you defend the colours of your country. You can hate or love me for my actions yesterday, but I am a warrior and I will do it again when needed to protect our boys on the pitch against unjustified decisions,” Stimac tweeted.</p>



<p>The rain-drenched first half was meandering to its conclusion with the home side leading 2-0 after two Sunil Chhetri goals. But a moment of indiscretion from Stimac suddenly livened up the proceedings.</p>



<p>Stimac, a vastly experienced coach and player, chose to interfere when Pakistan player Abdullah Iqbal was ready to make a throw-in. Stimac tried to pull back the ball from the player, sparking wild reactions from some visiting players as well as some coaching staff.</p>



<p>The referee Prajwal Chhetri and other match officials had to intervene to separate the intensely sparring individuals.</p>



<p>As the scuffle was brought under control referee Chhetri showed red card to Stimac, as per the football rules, for interrupting with the actions of an opposition player deliberately.</p>



<p>Stimac could not stand on the sideline for the rest of the match, with former India defending Mahesh Gawli doing duty on the touchline.</p>



<p>A few players from India and Pakistan teams too were flashed yellow cards for intervening unnecessarily in the episode.</p>



<p>After rout of Pakistan, India assistant coach Gawli said the red card might appear a bit harsh on his senior, but the referee had to go by the book.</p>



<p>“Yeah, it was an offence that if you go by the book often attracts a red card. But yeah, but then we feel that it might have been a bit harsh on the coach,” Gawli had said during the post-match press conference.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/igor-stimac-on-getting-red-card-for-interrupting-pakistan-player-i-will-do-it-again-when-needed-to-protect-our-boys/">Igor Stimac on getting red card for interrupting Pakistan player: ‘I will do it again when needed to protect our boys’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://uks.online.mills.edu/igor-stimac-on-getting-red-card-for-interrupting-pakistan-player-i-will-do-it-again-when-needed-to-protect-our-boys/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chhetri closes in on Messi after brilliant hattrick in IND vs PAK match</title>
		<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/chhetri-closes-in-on-messi-after-brilliant-hattrick-in-ind-vs-pak-match/</link>
					<comments>https://uks.online.mills.edu/chhetri-closes-in-on-messi-after-brilliant-hattrick-in-ind-vs-pak-match/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://uks.online.mills.edu/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lionel Messi (103), who won the 2022 FIFA World Cup with Argentina, former Iran star Ali Daei (109) and Portugal&#8217;s Cristiano Ronaldo (123) are above Chhetri in that list. Taking advantage of a blunder from Pakistan goalkeeper Saqib Hanif, Chhetri latched onto a poor pass to slot the opener in the 10th-minute. Then in the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/chhetri-closes-in-on-messi-after-brilliant-hattrick-in-ind-vs-pak-match/">Chhetri closes in on Messi after brilliant hattrick in IND vs PAK match</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lionel Messi (103), who won the 2022 FIFA World Cup with Argentina, former Iran star Ali Daei (109) and Portugal&#8217;s Cristiano Ronaldo (123) are above Chhetri in that list.</p>



<p>Taking advantage of a blunder from Pakistan goalkeeper Saqib Hanif, Chhetri latched onto a poor pass to slot the opener in the 10th-minute. Then in the 16th-minute, a hand ball in the Pakistan penalty box gifted the hosts a penalty, which Chhetri shot to the left corner to make it 2-0. Then in the 74th-minute, Chhetri was fouled in the box and India once again received a penalty. Calm and cool, the veteran striker shot it towards the top left corner.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Here is the video of Chhetri&#8217;s hattrick:</h2>



<p>Meanwhile, a beautiful long ball by defender Anwar Ali saw Udanta Singh score his first goal since 2018 in the 81st-minute.Among the active players, Chhetri also has the third-most goals by an international player, with only Messi (103) and Ronaldo (123) ahead of him.</p>



<p>The match was also an ill-tempered clash and saw India head coach Igor Stimac receive a red card just before half-time, as he tried to take the ball from a Pakistan player to prevent him from taking a throw-in. The incident got both teams into a tussle and the Croatian was sent off. Reacting after the match, Stimac wrote on Twitter, &#8220;Football is all about passion, especially when you defend the colours of your country. You can hate or love me for my actions yesterday, but I am a warrior and I will do it again when needed to protect our boys on the pitch against unjustified decisions.&#8221;</p>



<p><a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/author/ht-sports-desk-101607439300849"></a>At HT Sports Desk, passionate reporters work round the clock to provide detailed updates from the world of sports. Expect nuanced match reports, previews,reviews, technical analysis based on statistics, the latest social media trends, expert opinions on cricket, football, tennis, badminton, hockey,motorsports, wrestling, boxing, shooting, athletics and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/chhetri-closes-in-on-messi-after-brilliant-hattrick-in-ind-vs-pak-match/">Chhetri closes in on Messi after brilliant hattrick in IND vs PAK match</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://uks.online.mills.edu/chhetri-closes-in-on-messi-after-brilliant-hattrick-in-ind-vs-pak-match/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is it Umran Malik’s time in Test matches for India?</title>
		<link>https://uks.online.mills.edu/is-it-umran-maliks-time-in-test-matches-for-india/</link>
					<comments>https://uks.online.mills.edu/is-it-umran-maliks-time-in-test-matches-for-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 13:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://uks.online.mills.edu/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2022 IPL Kolkata Knight Riders skipper Shreyas Iyer was undone by Umran Malik’s fine yorker. It wasn’t the delivery which dismissed Iyer that stood out but the set-up. Iyer had to face Malik who was bowling thunderbolts on his arrival to the crease. The seed of a short ball doubt was put into his...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/is-it-umran-maliks-time-in-test-matches-for-india/">Is it Umran Malik’s time in Test matches for India?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In 2022 IPL Kolkata Knight Riders skipper Shreyas Iyer was undone by Umran Malik’s fine yorker. It wasn’t the delivery which dismissed Iyer that stood out but the set-up. Iyer had to face Malik who was bowling thunderbolts on his arrival to the crease. The seed of a short ball doubt was put into his mind with the field and the balls before the dismissal. Iyer, rattled by the pace, just kept moving around the crease trying to find a solution and was eventually put out of his misery by the sheer pace of Malik.</p>



<p>On his day, with the right kind of backing, he can be lethal. Sunrisers Hyderabad didn’t use him properly for whatever reasons, but that doesn’t mean he should be in the ignored bin for too long. He has pace, he is young, and he needs a good captain and coach to use him effectively. The dismissal of Iyer in the IPL game displayed the right-arm quick has also got the smarts to set up a batter which might be useful in Test matches whilst bowling longer spells. He might be raw, but with good guidance and handling, he can deliver.</p>



<p>Given the recent WTC debacle, Indian selectors are looking to blood a few fresh faces and the tour of the West Indies will be a perfect opportunity for Umran Malik to showcase his skills with the red ball</p>



<p>In the absence of Jasprit Bumrah in the final India went with 35-year-old Umesh Yadav who was supposed to be the X-factor in the side with his extra pace. However, things did not go according to the plan for Rohit’s men on Day-1 which essentially cost the side the game. With age not on Umesh’s side and the next WTC final once again in England at Lords in conditions where spinners will probably not have a lot to say, India need to build another pace battery unit and the tour to the Caribbean will be the ideal start for Malik’s red ball career.</p>



<p>The pace bowler from Jammu and Kashmir played only a handful of seven first-class games in which he picked up 12 wickets at an economy of 4.46. However, the sample size is too small and he has shown the ability to hit hard lengths regularly in the IPL. In addition to overseas conditions, Malik will be a force to reckon with even in India with his extra pace, especially with the old ball.</p>



<p>The unknowns with him are obvious: does he have the ability to build spells, bowl 20 overs a day. Given the quality of West Indies batters in recent times this might be the ideal opportunity for Malik to learn on the job.</p>



<p><strong>Mukesh Kumar-The reliable one</strong></p>



<p>India got undone in the final by Scott Boland whose biggest strength is his discipline with the line and length, and how he weaves in the subtle variations which was key in taking down Virat Kohli. After Ishant Sharma (in his final phase when India used him as a stock bowler), India are lacking someone who can hit one spot consistently for the entire day and bowl long spells.</p>



<p>Bengal’s Mukesh Kumar is the ideal candidate for the role. He has been piling wickets in first-class cricket for the last few seasons. He picked up 123 wickets from just 33 games at an average of 21.49. He also has been in the reserves of the WTC squad. His ability to bowl long spells and keep things tight from his end irrespective of the conditions might allow the other quickmen to take a breather and keep the batsmen honest. In overseas Tests, India has struggled to dry the run flow when partnerships built up.</p>



<p><strong>Arshdeep Singh- better investment than Unadkat?</strong></p>



<p>Since Zaheer Khan the men in blue have also been lacking in quality left-arm-seamer. Though Jaydev Unadkat has been carried along the squad in the last few series, the management seems to see him as more of a horses for courses option rather than a regular in the team. Arshdeep, who has been plying his trade in county cricket for Kent might be the suitable option for that role.</p>



<p>Similar to Malik, Arshdeep too has limited experience in first class cricket. He played seven games and picked up 21 wickets with an average of 35.19. However, he has shown in the past his ability to swing the new white ball and his stint at Kent will give him exposure to bowling in overseas conditions and bowling with the Dukes ball.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu/is-it-umran-maliks-time-in-test-matches-for-india/">Is it Umran Malik’s time in Test matches for India?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://uks.online.mills.edu">UKS Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://uks.online.mills.edu/is-it-umran-maliks-time-in-test-matches-for-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
